dariuszhanc@gmail.pl +48888035509 linkedin.com/in/dariuszhanc

SKILL SAMPLES - github.com/undersoft-org - github.com/unirecon-net

### Summary

Over 15 years of experience in commercial programming. Broad spectrum of practical knowledge and wisdom in areas like .NET, Just-in-time Compilation, Design Patterns, Algorithm Optimization, Data Science, Big Data, Machine Learning, Distributed Systems and more. Always pursuing to be up to date with modern technologies. Co-founder and creator of functional IT solutions aware that business value matters and focused on achieving it. Scientist for whom a programming language or technology is not a problem because it understands the machine and can think like one.

Motto: "Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication" - Leonardo da Vinci

### Experience

## Fullstack Software Developer

Undersoft - github.com/undersoft-org/undersoft Apr 2023 - Present - Self employment

Development of modern enterprise cloud web applications with CI/CD on Azure, IBM cloud, AWS using Kubernetes, .NET 8, Blazor Web Assembly, MAUI Blazor in design patterns CQRS with Event Store and explicit Read/Write databases, DDD, N-Tier (4-Tier), Microservices with application client, application server, operational data service and data storage tiers communication protocols based on Rest API, OData, GRPC

#### Senior Software Engineer

Nicman Group – Beckman Coulter R&D Contribution - nicmangroup.com Nov 2022 – Apr 2023 – Employment contract

Beckman Coulter Inc. Hemoglobin Research & Development Department. Project HFI - Hemoglobin Flow Imaging Apartature. Member of team responsible for research and development of Data Processing Module contains Data Storage Manager (Python), Patch Classification Module – Inference in area of Image Classification Algorithms (Python / C#), Raw Data Module, Image Processing Module.

#### Independent Software Developer

Benefit Systems S.A – Multisport card – benefitsystems.pl Jun 2021 – May 2022 – Contract

Development of Service Provider / Orchestrator for Enterprise Ecostystem in area of user consents and agrrements provided to brokers and systems in areas like marketing automation, infoline, legal office etc. Software Architecture based on DDD, CQRS, Distributed ORM deployed on AWS cloud using CI/CD processes and Scrum project management methodology

### Advanced Computing Technology Developer

Unirecon Tczew – Deep technologies Mar 2020 – May 2021 - Self-employed Development of Deep-Tech solutions and embedded software programming on freelance contracts.

### Chief Technology Officer (CTO)

Nethansa sp z o.o. Sopot - E-commerce automation – <u>nethansa.com</u> Jul 2016 – Feb 2020 (3 years 8 months) - Contract

Co-founder and Nethansa GmbH Munchen shareholder. Creator of Nethansa's base algorithms and first versions of a functional service oriented application Webbiz (later renamed to Clipperon). Responsible for product development in broad wholesystem context. Influencing software architecture, technology, implementation methodologies and standards. Coaching and mentoring members of the Team in area of development, architecture and selfgrowth. Leading and supervising process of aquisition and implementation of projects under grants for innovations and research and development.

### Information Technology Manager

Stokki sp. z o.o. Gdańsk – International trading Feb 2015 – Jul 2016 (1 year 6 months) – Full-time

Management of IT and computer systems in international Polish-German trading company. Design, development and implementation of: software, computer and cash register hardware (POS), network solutions, surveillance and alarm systems etc. Controlling and evaluating IT and electronic data operations. Staff training.

#### Software Architect

Undersoft Tczew – Digital transformation Jan 2013 – Jan 2018 (5 years 1 month) – Self-employed

Design of distributed system architecture and services programming on freelance contracts.

## • Information Technology Manager

Jukado sp. z o.o. Tczew – Grocery store chain Jan 2012 – Jan 2015 (3 years 1 month) – Full-time

Management of IT and computer systems in the headquarters and branches of the grocery store chain. Design, development and implementation of: software, computer and cash register hardware (POS), network solutions, surveillance and alarm systems etc. Controlling and evaluating IT and electronic data operations. Staff training.

### Software Developer

Undersoft Tczew - Digital transformation Mar 2006 - Jan 2013 (7 years 4 months) - Self-employed

Fullstack software development on freelance contracts.

### Head of Logistics Department

MIKROSTYK S.A. Gniew – Leading metal stamping producer – <u>mikrostyk.com</u> Jan 2009 – Jan 2010 (1 years 1 month) – Full-time

Planning and managing logistics, warehouse, transportation and customer services. Directing, optimizing and coordinating full order cycle. International cooperation and negotiations with suppliers and customers.

## Computer Scientist

MIKROSTYK S.A Gniew – Leading metal stamping producer – <u>mikrostyk.com</u> Feb 2006 – Feb 2009 (3 years 1 month) – Full-time

Administrating information technology and computer systems in manufacturing company. Design, development and implementation of: software, computer hardware, network solutions, surveillance and alarm systems etc. Controlling and evaluating IT and electronic data operations. Staff training.

## Education

The State University of Applied Sciences in Elblag

incomoplete, Database design and application programming 2004 – 2006

Economic School Complex in Tczew

Trader technician, Economics of trade 1999 – 2004

### Certifications

 MCSA Microsoft Sql Server 2000 Associate - Microsoft March 2005

• Cisco CCNA Routing and Switching - Cisco

October 2008

• **Leadership psychology -** Mateusz Grzesiak – <u>mateuszgrzesiak.com</u> December 2018

Achievement psychology - Mateusz Grzesiak – <u>mateuszgrzesiak.com</u>
 October 2019

#### Skills

#### **Industry Knowledge**

- Object Oriented Programming (OOP)
- Programming models
- Domain Driven Developmnet (DDD)
- Command Query Responsibility Segregation (CQRS)
- Event Sourcing
- Distributed Systems
- Software Architecture
- Optimization
- Design Patterns
- Machine Learning
- Computer Networking
- Web Applications

- Data Structures
- Unstructured Data
- Virtual Private Network (VPN)
- Agile Software Development
- Research and Development (R&D)
- Virtual Actor Programming
- Microservices
- Software Testing
- Virtualization
- Containerization
- Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI)

Technology	Proficiency		
• C#	Mastery	• Java Intermediate	
<ul> <li>T-SQL</li> </ul>	Advanced	• Embedded C Intermediate	
• C/C++	Advanced	• Python Intermediate	

JavaScript ES6 Intermediate	ASP.NET Core			
HTML5/CSS Intermediate	ASP.NET MVC			
CUDA ntermediate	ASP.NET Blazor			
MSIL Intermediate	• XML			
Assembler Elementary	• JSON			
.NET Standard	<ul> <li>SOAP</li> </ul>			
.NET Core	• RESTful			
Tools & Frameworks				
Windows Server	SignalR			
<ul> <li>Linux (Debian based distributions)</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>TensorFlow</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Microsoft SQL Server</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Docker</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>MySQL (MariaDB)</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Kubernetes</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>MongoDB</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>VirtualBox</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Apache Hadoop</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>RabbitMQ</li> </ul>			
Apache Kafka	• Redis			
Hypertable DB	<ul> <li>Microsoft IIS</li> </ul>			
(Google's Bigtable Database Design)	<ul> <li>Apache HTTP Server</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>.NET Orleans Framework</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Qt Creator IDE</li> </ul>			
(Microsoft Research)	<ul> <li>Visual Studio IDE</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>.NET Entity Framework</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Visual Code IDE</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>.NET Framework</li> </ul>	Eclipse IDE			
<ul> <li>Accord.NET ML Framework</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Android Studio IDE</li> </ul>			
Interpersonal Skills				
Team Management	Team Coaching & Mentoring			
Can-do Attitude	<ul> <li>Interpersonal Communication</li> </ul>			
Other Skills				
<ul> <li>Centralized Version Control - SVN</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Parallel Computing</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Distributed Version Control - Git</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Shared Memory</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>High Performance Computing (HPC)</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Application Programming Interfaces</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Algorithm Optimization</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Network Protocol Design</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Low Level Programming</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Embedded Software Programming</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Network Programming</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Azure DevOps</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Concurrent Programming</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Amazon MWS API's</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Dynamic Programming</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Amazon AWS API's</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Virtual Actor Model</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Full-Stack Development</li> </ul>			
<ul> <li>Digital Transformation</li> </ul>				

# Selected projects

 Innovative solutions in the field of product classification and price list forecasting based on Machine Learning. Co-financed by European Funds as part of Pro-innovative services for enterprises

Jun 2018 - Aug 2019

Machine Learning solution operating as independent scalable microservices with RESTful API's. It included the services of clustering similar products, forecasting prices, predicting the value of planned short- and long-term sales.

more information at nethansa.com/sales-intellligence/

 Webbiz (later Nethansa Clipperon) - Automation of sales and logistics on European Amazon marketplaces - Startup project

Oct 2015 - Oct 2018

E-commerce system that integrates with retailers warehouse enabling automated sale on Amazon marketplaces. Automation of the process from the warehouse in the company's system through sales on European Amazon marketplaces, ending with parcel collection by courier and delivery to the customer.

more information at nethansa.com/clipperon/

 Distributed system for central management of sales and turnover of goods in canteens, placed in prisons and detention centers in the Pomeranian. Integrated with the internet service of ordering goods for convicts assembled in canteens

Oct 2009 - Jun 2011

Subcontractor responsible for the design, develop and implementation of the system in part of the order granted to Jukado sp z o.o. as a result of a tender submitted by Institutions of Budget Economy BIGB Baltica Gdańsk. As part of the implementation of the regulation of the Minister of Justice on the sale and turnover of goods in canteens placed in prisons and detention centers.

• Spectrum Base 2000 - Modular network software for managing logistics and manufacturing processes. Digitally transformed from processes implemented by the Mikrostyk company during ISO 9001 and ISO TS certification.

Jun 2006 - May 2009

The system supports processes in the areas:

- Logistics: sale orders, forecasts, purchase orders, warehouse management of materials and finished products, shipping.
- Production: technological operations, production orders. workstation orders (execute operations, tool settings, machine breakdowns, quality control, assembling, packing), reporting workstation orders on terminals
- Additional data exchange integration with Syteline ERP and Trawers ERP planning and accounting software

## Languages

 polish native • **english** professional

• **german** elementary

# Organizations

## • Pomeranian Voivodeship Parliament of Student Councils

Member of the Board Dec 2001 - Oct 2002

## • Youth City Council of Tczew

Chairman Sep 2001 - Sep 2002

## • Youth City Council of Tczew

Councillor Sep 2000 - Sep 2002

# Interests & hobbies

- Programming models
- Data structure algorithms
- 3D CAD Modeling
- Prediction algorithms
- Electronic design
- Experimental phisics
- 3D Printing
- Skiing
- Internet of Things

- Bass guitar
- Dogtrekking

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).